{
    "list":[
        {"Question":"A","Answer":"Apple"},
        {"Question":"A","Answer":"Acorn"},
        {"Question":"B","Answer":"Bread"},
        {"Question":"B","Answer":"Bean"},
        {"Question":"C","Answer":"Cucumber"},
        {"Question":"C","Answer":"Carrot"},
        {"Question":"D","Answer":"Daikon"},
        {"Question":"D","Answer":"Date"},
        {"Question":"E","Answer":"Elderberry"},
        {"Question":"E","Answer":"Egg"}
    ],
  "dic": {
    "A": [ "Apple", "Acorn" ],
    "B": [ "Bread", "Bean" ],
    "C": [ "Cucumber", "Carrot" ],
    "D": [ "Daikon", "Date" ],
    "E": [ "Elderberry", "Egg" ]
  },
  "table": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "phonics": "A",
      "word": "apple"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "phonics": "A",
      "word": "acorn"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "phonics": "B",
      "word": "bread"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "phonics": "B",
      "word": "bean"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "phonics": "C",
      "word": "cucumber"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "phonics": "C",
      "word": "carrot"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "phonics": "D",
      "word": "daikon"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "phonics": "D",
      "word": "date"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "phonics": "E",
      "word": "elderberry"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "phonics": "E",
      "word": "egg"
    }
  ]

}
